Timothy LaRoy Jr.

8236 Dodd Cir Fort Meade, MD 20755 timlaroy93@gmail.com (703) 909 - 5511 **Github:** https://github.com/KrombopulOs **Portfolio:** https://krombopulOs.github.io/portfolio

ABOUT

Marine veteran with a passion for helping others and learning about the world of technology. A proven leader and team member with experience working successfully in team and individual environments. Possesses the drive and resourcefulness to find information, gain knowledge, and provide solutions to ensure overwhelming success.

FORMAL EDUCATION

Concordia University - Chicago - M.S. Applied Exercise Science (Jan 2020 - Dec 2020) American Military University - B.S. Sports & Health Science (Jan 2018 - Dec 2019)

CERTIFICATIONS, COURSEWORK, and SKILLS LEARNED

COMPTIA A+ - in progress, testing in Sept 2022

Google Data Analytics Specialization

R, SQL, Excel, Data Handling, tableau, big Query

Google IT Support Specialization

Networking, Security, linux, windows, mobile OS's, troubleshooting

Java Programming Specialization - *Duke University*

➤ Object oriented programming, problem solving, CSV file reading

Python Programming Specialization - *University of Michigan*

Jupyter Notebooks, JSON, Django, Tesseract

WORK HISTORY

Stay at Home Father - Sept 2020 - Aug 2022

Used advanced time management, resource allocation, and non-standard communication techniques in order to maintain human life on a daily basis as well as dealing with hazardous waste disposal.

MCCS Quantico - Russell Knox Fitness Center - Fitness Specialist

Mar 2021 - May 2021 POC: Kim Ryan (571) 305-4581

Programmed and executed individual and group fitness training.

Online Strength Coach (self employed)

Jun 2018 - Mar 2021

- **▶** Directly oversaw the training of multiple types of athletes and clients
- Identified and corrected movement dysfunctions resolving acute pain

USMC - Search and Rescue/Maintenance Control Chief

Oct 2012 - Oct 2017 POC: N/A (unit disbanded in 2020)

- Responsible for 40+ Marines, 4 aircraft, and a multi-million dollar account
- → Organized daily operations for squadron and oversaw the technical training of the unit leading to highest squadron readiness in all of Marine Corps